{
    "subject": "Napoleon_Louis_Bonaparte",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Charlotte_Napol\u00e9one_Bonaparte",
    "human_readable": "Napoleon Louis Bonaparte is married to Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858996272087097,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance to the marriage between Napoleon Louis Bonaparte and Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9704102873802185,
            "question": "Was Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte related to Napoleon Louis Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9614977240562439,
            "question": "What were some of the key events that happened during the marriage of Napoleon Louis Bonaparte and Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9595767855644226,
            "question": "Who was Napoleon Louis Bonaparte married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9542838931083679,
            "question": "Were there any children born from the marriage of Napoleon Louis Bonaparte and Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9492005109786987,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about the relationship between Napoleon Louis Bonaparte and Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9434347152709961,
            "question": "To whom did Napoleon Louis Bonaparte have a marriage with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8693109154701233,
            "question": "What is the name of Napoleon Louis Bonaparte's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8539642691612244,
            "question": "What is the full name of Napoleon Louis Bonaparte's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8439927697181702,
            "question": "Who was Napoleon Louis Bonaparte?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Napoleon Louis Bonaparte is married to Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte.",
            "html": "yago_8996_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full name of Napoleon Louis Bonaparte's wife?",
            "html": "yago_8996_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Napoleon Louis Bonaparte's wife?",
            "html": "yago_8996_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Napoleon Louis Bonaparte have a marriage with?",
            "html": "yago_8996_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8996_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Napoleon Louis Bonaparte (born 11 October 1804) married Charlotte Napol\u00e9one Bonaparte on 23 July 1826."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}